Hey.
Department
of Public Safety.
Mr. Dennison?
Vincent Dennison is
a registered sex offender.
The sooner I can
verify his address,
the sooner I can
leave him alone.
- You've been here for...
- A year and a half.
Have you used any aliases
in the past six months?
- No.
- "No."
What do you do?
I mean, for fun.
Just...
Go to church.
I attend
a support group.
Uh-huh. What kind
of support group?
Come on, man,
you know.
What do you think about,
Vincent?
I mean sexual thoughts.
- I don't know.
- Come on.
Everyone has
sexual thoughts.
You ain't supposed
to ask me that.
That's not on
the questionnaire.
You're right.
- How've your moods been?
- Good.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
You taking
your medication?
- Yeah.
- Good. It's important to do that.
Any feelings that might
lead you to do something
you don't want to do?
No.
How would you cope
with a feeling
that might lead you
to stray?
I'll settle down
with a nice girl.
Does that sound realistic
to you, Vincent?
I don't know.
What do you think about
when you masturbate?
You think about settling
down with a nice girl?
Or you think about
holding her down?
Morning.
She starts today.
You'll be sharing
a desk and a car.
Oh, good good good good.
Good.
- You want to meet her?
- You know I got another month, right?
Send in Allison, please.
You can retire
right this minute if you want to.
- You've earned it.
- No. No, Bobby, no.
No, I have not
earned this.
Mmm.
- Hi.
- Allison Lowry,
this is Errol Babbage.
Mr. Babbage,
it's a pleasure to meet you.
Yeah, no need to be so wonderful.
You got the job...
- apparently.
- Errol,
would you excuse us
for a moment, please?
Surely, yeah.
Okay.
Good, very good.
Usually, I'd ask
a seasoned guy like Errol
to help you
stay out of trouble.
In this situation,
things are the other
way around.
Any questions,
just ask.
Thank you.
You're not gonna learn
anything from them...
except how
to keep your job.
That's yours. This is your desk.
Move that over if you want.
- You coming?
- Oh, yeah.
We have a young man who just
moved here from out of state.
- What did he do?
- Rape.
Second degree,
plea bargain.
I don't care what he did.
I care what he's gonna do.
You know, these people
are registered as a...
as a courtesy
to the public,
to the victims, to the people who
testified against them.
Also because... because of what
they're capable of...
- Mm-hm.
...because of their potential.
Registering them is one thing,
but telling the future,
that's... that's
something else.
We're fortune tellers.
Predict wrong,
people die.
I was misunderstood.
The male is more sexually
aggressive by nature.
It's a way of passing on
their genetic material.
"Misunderstood."
His mother couldn't
buy her off is what happened.
Like she did with
all the others.
- What's your name, hon?
- Beatrice Bell.
- What was it? Beatrice Bell? Nice.
So tell me,
Beatrice Bell,
how often does Edmund here
pass on his
genetic material?
- I don't know.
- Mm-hmm.
Sometimes too often?
Sometimes when
things don't...
quite function...
right,
you get the blame?
I don't think
this is appropriate.
Then maybe you
should wait outside.
You know, you can call me
when you've had enough of this guy.
I'll help you get rid of him.
Okay?
Hey.
What's that?
Did you do this?
You guys finished
with the survey?
- Did you do this?
- And by the way, I brush...
Hey, did you do this?
You're a hitter,
aren't you?
Likes the sound of knuckles
on a woman's body.
Maybe she enjoys it.
Maybe I do too.
Okay, well, hey.
All right, Edmund, okay.
I'm just coming... I'm here
to welcome you to the state.
So, welcome.
What are you circling?
I keep track of offenses
that might have been committed
by one of my people.
If a pattern develops,
or something occurs to me
that could help the police,
I pass it on.
Those questions
weren't on the form.
Mr. Babbage?
They were invasive.
Compulsive rapists,
opportunistic rapists,
armpit rapists,
date rapists,
fetishists,
exhibitionists,
frotteurs,
molesters of animals,
molesters of children...
You better tell me now
if you're too squeamish for this job.
Call your mother,
have her come pick you up.
So what are you
gonna do now?
I mean, when you retire?
I'm not retiring.
I'm being let go.
You could use
a new look.
Get some of that hair
out of your face.
I'll get the check.
Don't worry, the department's
paying for this.
Unlawful imprisonment,
attempted sexual battery,
three counts..."
- Sit up, please.
- Did two years.
Could have been much worse,
except for the plea bargain.
Partner executed in August.
For attempted battery?
- No, murder.
- This way, please.
Yep, they slowly
mutilated these women
till they died...
took over a week.
And then they
cut off their feet,
their legs, their hands
their arms,
their tongues,
their ears,
- and their hair.
- Jesus.
It was all over the news.
The one executed is Paul Gerard.
Partner who rolled on him
was his wife.
We're talking about
Paul Gerard's wife?
Well, she's using
her maiden name now.
Aren't you, Viola?
Ow!
Sorry.
You okay?
Ah, Viola is my favorite
registrant, aren't you, Viola?
You should let me do
something about that gray.
You're never
touching me.
You can take care
of the registration.
I got a couple
things to do.
He enjoyed that.
So, um, how long
have you worked here?
A week longer than that last time
I was asked that question.
What's wrong?
I was as much a victim
as those women.
I'm not here
to go over that.
Paul would try out
behavior on me,
things he...
later did to those three.
He...
he crept up behind me and
grabbed me around my neck.
I was told
to widen my eyes...
just so...
in surprise.
Then...
he'd...
drag me off
to the bedroom
where he'd smother me
with a plastic bag.
The only reason
I'm alive...
is because my death
would have led to him.
He didn't kill me.
He killed who I was.
Usually, Mr. Babbage
comes to my home...
three, four times a month.
- What does he want?
- Same questions...
over and over.
I'll make sure that he...
he leaves you alone.
And I'll be doing
things differently.
Did she say
I saw her last week?
Yes.
Did she say she
was innocent?
Did she say she got off on what
her husband did to those ladies?
I can't tell if you're
just green or indifferent.
Is indifference the same
as wishing you'd come up for air
once in a while?
I've got 18 days to teach you
everything I can.
I want you to see something,
feel something.
This is Viola's
childhood farm.
Now she says
she was the victim?
This is where
the real victims suffered.
Three girls
known murdered.
Three other girls disappeared
about the same time
she and Paul were caught.
Tried to get her
to confess,
take me to where
they buried them.
I want to give
their folks some peace.
I've always suspected
their bones
scattered all over
these fields.
This isn't a registrant.
Yeah, the daughter disappeared
from a college campus
six years ago.
I always suspected
Paul and Viola.
Don't tell them
I got fired.
Errol's visits
are difficult for me,
but Ann seems to find
some comfort in them.
I'm grateful to him
for that.
That's her.
That's Abigail.
- She's pretty.
- Mm-hmm.
We don't know
what happened.
Errol's the only one who promised
we would one day.
That we'd know.
The only one.
Why are we staying here?
We're just a couple hours from home.
We're not going home.
I have a little light
reading for you.
Oh, and if I didn't
already tell you,
always remember
to carry a fresh shirt.
Very important.
Oh!
Welcome.
I'll have the nacho rapists,
the buffalo wing rapists...
the molesters of fried
mozzarella with some...
rib fetishists.
I circled them all for you.
- Hey, here's to Errol!
- To Errol!
Where is Errol, by the way?
Where'd you go
last night?
Did you look
in that book I gave you?
Yes.
Good, because I want you
to always remember
people like Paul and Viola
Gerard don't just tell lies,
they are lies.
In public, they're decent,
socially-responsible folk
who look you in the eye,
but never long enough
to make you uncomfortable.
They shake your hand,
pat you on the back,
but never overdo it.
They're Christian if you are,
they swear if you do,
and they do this because
people like you
wrongly believe
that public presentation
tells us all about
private lives.
It tells us nothing.
It hides everything.
And what about you,
Mr. Babbage?
Tell me about
your double life.
What do you think about?
I think about a girl
who didn't come home,
what I might have missed,
and if I miss something again,
who's next?
That's a good boy.
Bye, Harriet. See you tomorrow.
See ya.
This next
registrant's a fellow
by the name
of Glenn Custis.
He's turned his
perversions into a business.
He's a pornographer...
movies, magazines.
He also runs
a little dominion.
- What's a dominion?
- You'll see.
Why don't you look down that way?
I'll go this way.
Hey.
I'm okay.
Do you know where Glenn...
I'm looking
for Glenn Custis.
Yeah! Mmm...
Rasputin here
says Custis is out.
Glenn, this guy's
looking for you.
Glenn?
I'm not Glenn.
Nice hands.
Nice fingers.
- You're white.
- Let go.
Let go, let go.
Hey hey hey hey hey,
look at me.
Look at me, look at me, look at me.
You know who this is?
This is one of
Custis's girls.
That's right, one of
Glenn's girl... Look at me.
Just look at me.
Look in my eyes.
Tell Custis
I'm looking for him.
Fuck.
So you're not seeing anyone,
I mean anyone
who stayed.
What did I tell you about
the personal stuff?
Okay.
Whatever.
It's just that l...
I didn't see a spare toothbrush
or a man's razor, so...
But I did see a large
pea coat hanging there.
Shiny elbows and
missing buttons, so...
A smoker. It's not exactly
your style, I don't think.
But I guess it suited
your needs for the time.
Do you ever just have
a normal conversation?
This is normal
conversation.
No, I mean,
"Hey... hey, how are you?
Nice weather, huh?
Hey, thanks for the drink."
You don't talk,
you pump.
The fire has consumed over 1700 acres
and 14 houses.
In other news, police
are investigating
the disappearance
of Harriet Wells.
The 17-year-old is believed
to have been abducted
in the Paradise Hills area
sometime yesterday.
Harriet's parents made
a plea in help
tracing their daughter's
whereabouts.
We just want
our daughter to come home.
We want her to come back.
She's our everything,
our whole life.
If anyone knows
where she is,
please just help me
bring my baby home.
Police have no suspects
at this time.
If you have any
information...
It's one of my flock.
I know it. I missed something.
Errol, slow down.
- Are you watching this?
- Yeah, I just turned it on.
- I'm not gonna go out like this.
I'm not gonna have
a mista...
God damn it.
- Are you okay?
- No.
No. No, I'm not okay.
I'm not okay.
Errol, you can't
take this personally.
You take this stuff
personally!
I've been on this job 18 years.
You haven't even fucking started.
You haven't even started.
...may have been the last to see her.
While friends and family
continue their own search efforts... #
Harriet's parents
made a plea today
for help in tracing
their daughter's whereabouts,
but, investigators say,
false tips continue
to complicate
the investigation.
Sorry about
the phone call.
Department
of Public Safety.
All right,
come with me.
Can you wait here,
please?
- Officer in charge?
- Yes.
Can I talk to you a second?
Something I want to show you...
Babbage, we're on it.
There are over 40 registered
sexual offenders...
- I know.
...within two miles of here.
I know.
We're handling it.
...responding to the possible 211.
2110 Emerson.
Just hope and pray.
You're right, you're right.
You can take off, okay?
Sure, okay.
I don't know what else to do.
What'd they say?
They're gonna
give me a medal.
- Really?
- Yeah, it's in the mail.
- Have a nice day.
- Thank you.
Did you see who was...
was sitting there?
The newspaper...
left it there?
I don't think there was
anybody sitting there.
All right.
- Did you put this here?
- No.
Someone left this here.
They left it for me.
How do you know
somebody left it for you?
Look at it... it's circled.
It's folded just like me.
Everything's the same.
Look. Don't don't don't
don't... don't touch.
This is the one
I bought.
See that?
Each of those
are offenders.
Red ones committed violent sexual acts
against teenage girls
or young women.
We'll start with
the registrants
that are closest
to the missing girl.
It could take weeks to
track down all these people.
Someone I know has her.
Someone who knows me.
Someone on
my registry.
Did she meet
a boy here?
A friend?
Was someone waiting
for her here?
Did someone see?
Between 4:00, 4:30,
you're the only engine on that track?
Yeah.
Car was white...
light color, anyways.
Newish.
Shit, maybe even Jap.
She was talking to somebody
in the car, but hell,
looked like she was just
trying to catch a ride.
Did you see him?
Did you see the driver?
- The guy she was talking to?
- Nah, we didn't see anyone.
There was a glare
on the windshield.
But you got it wrong.
She wasn't talking to the driver.
She was talking to someone
in the passenger seat.
Harriet talks to someone
on the passenger side.
That means we're
looking for a team.
Could be an old team,
could be a brand-new team.
Teams are glued together
by common sexual appetites
and fetishes.
So you hit the files.
I'll hit the phones.
I'll see who's quit a job,
changed their patterns.
I'll listen to their voices.
Hello?
You're looking for abductors,
rape or assault charges.
Any perps with victims
or MOs that match,
you red-flag it,
give it to me.
Can I talk to your boss
to confirm that?
If you think
that's really necessary.
Put your boss on, Randy.
Allison?
You know, I got
a phone call today
from a very agitated
sheriff's investigator.
It seems a girl
has disappeared.
And you were out
at her house?
Errol thinks one of
the registrants may be involved.
And how did Errol
come up with that one?
Someone circled an article
in the newspaper
and left it
for him to find.
Errol was a no-show at his
retirement party the other night.
I'm not sure
I understand.
These guys here are all familiar
with Errol's routines
and his habits.
Like how he dissects
the newspapers, for instance.
There was talk at the party
of getting back at him.
You think someone here
circled the article?
Yeah. Could be.
I mean, he doesn't have
a lot of friends around here.
Well, maybe not.
Are you gonna tell him?
You're gonna tell him.
Oh, and this
abduction thing...
has nothing to do with
what you're being paid for.
We're not police officers...
we're public servants.
All right?
So we have 40 offenders
within a two-mile radius,
89 within a five-mile
radius.
We're gonna hit
every single one of 'em.
Shouldn't we narrow
down the list first?
No, I want to
start now.
I'm gonna call it a day.
Yeah, you do that.
Just call it a day.
Two months... that's how long
you're gonna last.
But why should this job
be any different than the others?
I'm not one of
your registrants, Errol.
Just lay off
the personal stuff.
Your mother says
you spook easily.
- You talked to my mother?
- Among others.
Said you change jobs at about
the same rate you change men.
Does privacy mean anything
to you, Errol?
You are a nosy person,
my friend.
He didn't just leave that
newspaper for me.
He left it for you too.
When they find
Harriet's body in a month,
you'll be the one sitting
at this desk, not me.
Police are investigating
the disappearance...
Ahem.
Police have
no suspects...
Hello?
- Matt?
Hi, it's Allison Lowry...
from the department.
Ah, the new girl
in town.
Uh, the new girl.
Yeah.
Listen, I have to ask you,
do you know if people
in the department are taunting Errol?
- No.
- What about that...
the gag with the newspaper?
With the circling?
No no no, none of us.
Wasn't me. No.
- Not you either?
- No.
Okay, I was wrong.
All right, well, I'll see you
tomorrow at work, Allison.
- You have a good...
- Well... but, hey?
Since I have you
on the phone,
um, what else can you
tell me about Errol?
Well, he likes
to circle newspapers.
Right, I've noticed.
- Well, Errol's a good guy.
- Mm-hmm.
When he started,
he was great.
- Yeah.
- It was this one case...
a young girl named
Abigail taken,
and he got obsessed
by the whole thing
and, oh, he got in some
serious trouble that time.
He started carrying
a gun around
and we don't carry guns.
It's not part
of our job.
Well, thanks, Matt.
I appreciate it.
- Have a good night.
- Good night.
She was friendly, outgoing,
usually got along with everyone.
I don't think she ran away,
but if she did,
she should really come back.
Hey, Harriet,
you're on TV.
Miss you, Harriet.
Please come home.
Oh my God!
What are you
doing here, Errol?
Um...
uh, I have to
tell you something.
I have to tell you that...
that I have trouble
trusting...
I have trouble
trusting people.
Um, even non-registrants.
Um...
and I apologize for being
insensitive to your privacy,
even though a background check
is not entirely unreasonable.
Apology accepted.
You were right.
We got to narrow down
that list.
"Daniel Barden:
former CPA,
husband, father,
peeper, rapist,
once partnered
with Randall Adams."
"Carlos Hugo Catalan:
unlawful sexual intercourse
by fraud or fear,
believed to have had
different accomplices."
"James Ray Ward:
solicitation of an individual
under the age of 18 to engage
in sexual conduct,
assault with intent to
commit rape, second degree,
teamed with
Stuart Zimmerman."
What are you doing, James?
Am I gonna take this
to your parole officer?
You want me to do that?
Is that something I'm gonna have to do?
"Viola Gerard:
abuse of a minor
in a sexual performance,
aggravated sexual battery,
charged as an accomplice
to murder with Paul Gerard,
- got out on a plea bargain."
- Take care of the registration.
disappearance of
Harriet Wells, age 17.
Reported missing from her
parents' home in Paradise Hills...
You make a sound,
I'll kill you.
Hello?
No. Well,
this is his phone,
but Custis isn't here.
You can ask, but I'm
not gonna tell.
Hey, is this Babbage?
Yeah.
Uh-huh, this is Babbage.
Did you get
the newspaper?
Did you like the circles?
# I feel it in my heart #
# I feel it in my face #
# It's like a boom boom boom,
like a boom boom boom #
- # Going in my head... #
- Don't stop, baby.
Glenn Custis!
Custis!
- # I need your love... #
Who the fuck are you?
I'm looking for...
for Glenn Custis.
Are you sure?
Are you Glenn?
Glenn Custis!
Errol!
Custis!
Get in the car!
Get in!
Ahh!
I got friends in low places.
Isn't that right, Louis?
What are you doing here?
I just wanted to see how
the new job is shaping up.
I hear you do good work.
I don't handle
the photo center.
And the woman who does
won't be back until...
Who do you think
you're talking to?
Louis Louis.
Let's see, your hobby
is photography...
boys and girls at play,
as I remember.
And I do.
Look at that.
I don't do that
anymore.
He says he doesn't
do that anymore.
Should we believe him?
People get well.
Not my people.
She thinks she knows you, Louis,
but she doesn't, does she?
- No.
- No. No.
This room is the only reason
you took this shitty job.
Tell her.
Do you think that's
the missing girl?
Do you think
that's Harriet?
Not unless she has
two left feet.
There are at least three
people here, probably more.
Do you think he did this?
Did he cut these women?
I think he has a friend
in a funeral parlor or a morgue.
He probably did
the carving.
l...
I don't get this.
Well, you're probably
holding it wrong.
Yeah, like a centerfold.
Porno, you know.
This is all porno.
Just porno.
Every bit of it.
No.